=Betrayed Love=
= الحب المغدور =
=Episode 16=
= الحلقة 16 =
I have called you.
لقد دعاكم.
Why has your phone been off all along?
لماذا تم إيقاف تشغيل هاتفك طوال الوقت؟
If you still want to talk about us getting married,
إذا كنت لا تزال تريد التحدث عن زواجنا ،
don't bother.
لا تهتم.
I'm sorry. It was my fault last night.
أنا آسف.  كان خطأي الليلة الماضية.
I promise I won't bring it up again.
أعدك أنني لن أذكرها مرة أخرى.
I also said harsh words last night.
كما قلت كلمات قاسية الليلة الماضية.
You know, I've been in a bad mood recently.
أتعلم ، لقد كنت في مزاج سيء مؤخرًا.
I underestimated her.
أنا قللت من شأنها.
I didn't expect her to be so scheming.
لم أكن أتوقع أن تكون مكيدة للغاية.
Since we decided to do this,
منذ أن قررنا القيام بذلك ،
there has been no going back for us.
لم يكن هناك عودة بالنسبة لنا.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
If she doesn't die,
إذا لم تموت ،
we can't be a real couple.
لا يمكننا أن نكون زوجين حقيقيين.
She'll cement her position in the company in several days.
ستعزز موقعها في الشركة في غضون عدة أيام.
By then, you will have no chance.
بحلول ذلك الوقت ، لن يكون لديك فرصة.
I know a dead person poses no threats.
أعرف أن شخصًا ميتًا لا يشكل أي تهديد.
Now in this city,
الآن في هذه المدينة ،
it's not easy to make someone disappear completely,
ليس من السهل جعل شخص ما يختفي تمامًا ،
unless we can stage
ما لم نتمكن من المسرح
an accident.
حادث.
And it must be in the environment that Guan Xin is familiar with.
ويجب أن يكون في البيئة التي يعرفها Guan Xin.
No clues should be left.
لا ينبغي ترك أي أدلة.
That's a good idea.
إنها فكرةجيدة.
After Guan Xin falls asleep,
بعد نوم Guan Xin ،
I will turn on the gas
سأقوم بتشغيل الغاز
and pretend to be poisoned together.
وتتظاهر بالتسمم معًا.
I will ask for help after calculating the time.
سأطلب المساعدة بعد حساب الوقت.
In this way, we will stage a perfect accident.
بهذه الطريقة ، سنقوم بحادث مثالي.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
It's okay. I just burned myself.
حسنا.  أنا فقط أحرقت نفسي.
I can pretend to be a money-grubbing person for you.
يمكنني التظاهر بأنني شخص يبتلع المال من أجلك.
But I don't think Xu Jing will side with you
لكنني لا أعتقد أن Xu Jing سيقف معك
to deal with Shen Zhuo for the sake of her child.
للتعامل مع شين تشو من أجل طفلها.
Whatever the outcome is,
مهما كانت النتيجة ،
it is a tragedy in itself.
إنها مأساة في حد ذاتها.
Why do you find it hard to believe?
لماذا تجد صعوبة في تصديق؟
If one is too deep in love and loses herself,
إذا كان المرء غارقًا في الحب وفقد نفسه ،
she will end in tragedy easily.
ستنتهي بمأساة بسهولة.
If I hadn't been abroad when you chose to get married,
إذا لم أكن في الخارج عندما اخترت الزواج ،
I would certainly have voted him down.
كنت سأصوت عليه بالتأكيد.
Good hunters always appear prey.
يظهر الصيادون الجيدون دائمًا فريسة.
Didn't you come back to me?
ألم تعد لي؟
This is the best arrangement.
هذا هو أفضل ترتيب.
Xin, your plan itself has many variables.
شين ، خطتك نفسها بها العديد من المتغيرات.
What if Xu Jing really means to kill you?
ماذا لو قصد Xu Jing حقًا قتلك؟
In case anything goes wrong in the process...
في حالة حدوث أي خطأ في العملية ...
If I continue to live with him,
إذا واصلت العيش معه ،
I won't be at risk?
لن أكون في خطر؟
Do you have to end up like him in order to defeat him?
هل يجب أن ينتهي بك الأمر مثله حتى تهزمه؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
I just want people to be together with those they long for
أريد فقط أن يتواجد الناس مع من يتوقون إليهم
and to be completely split up with those they want to leave.
وأن ينفصلوا تمامًا عن أولئك الذين يريدون مغادرتهم.
And they mustn't take away things they are not entitled to.
ويجب ألا يأخذوا أشياء لا يحق لهم الحصول عليها.
Those are the shares my mom left me.
هذه هي الأسهم التي تركتها لي أمي.
You also try to control them?
أنت أيضا تحاول السيطرة عليهم؟
I'm short of money. I want to sell it. Can't I?
أنا أعاني من نقص في المال.  أريد بيعه.  لا أستطيع؟
Your mother left them to you to guarantee your basic life.
تركتها والدتك لك لتضمن لك حياتك الأساسية.
You can only get a little money if you sell them
يمكنك فقط الحصول على القليل من المال إذا قمت ببيعها
and you'll spend all the money in less than a year.
وستنفق كل الأموال في أقل من عام.
I will distribute dividends to you on time.
سوف أقوم بتوزيع الأرباح عليك في الوقت المحدد.
Just leave.
ارحل فقط.
OK.
نعم.
You overextended yourself!
لقد أرهقت نفسك!
You even try to interfere in the arrangement my mother made for me.
حتى أنك تحاول التدخل في الترتيب الذي جعلته والدتي لي.
What are you looking at? Get lost!
الى ماذا تنظرين؟  اغرب عن وجهي!
Since you enjoyed staying at Xu Jing's place,
بما أنك استمتعت بالإقامة في مكان Xu Jing ،
why did you come back?
لماذا عدت؟
It's strange. Did I say I wouldn't come back?
هذا غريب.  هل قلت إنني لن أعود؟
You can come back,
يمكنك العودة ،
but please don't trespass on my private space.
لكن من فضلك لا تتعدى على مساحتي الخاصة.
If you must stay overnight, there is the living room.
إذا كان يجب عليك البقاء بين عشية وضحاها ، فهناك غرفة المعيشة.